<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RFH</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Member Login</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_register">Register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="enterusername">"Enter Username"</string>
    <string name="enterpassword">"Enter Password"</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_testactivity">testactivity</string>
    <string name="brief_hospital">The Sir HN Reliance Foundation Hospital and Research Centre (RFH) was founded in 1925 as a 40 bed hospital. Between 1925 to 1950, it grew as an iconic centre for free and subsidized medical care for the community in Mumbai. It started its own in-house nursing trai-ning program - one of the first in the country in 1935. The Medical Research Society was opened in the 1970s. The Centre has been providing unparalleled community service for 87 years. Reliance Foundation has taken forward this spirit of affordable healthcare for everyone and has built a state-of-the-art hospital, comparable to the best in the world, to offer the quality healthcare at affordable cost. \n\nThe hospital campus comprises of three buildings with a total area of approximately 1 million sq. ft. The hospital has been planned and designed by one of the leading architectural firms of the world (Chicago based Perkin and Wills) and has been modelled on top American hospitals. The new facility has been designed in alignment with the following standards and regulatory requirements: AIA, ASHRAE, ADA, AERB, DCI (FDA) for blood bank, local compliances for engineering and construction, American standards\NFPA 99 for medical gases and other applicable local compliances for engineering and construction. Overall, the campus will house 345 beds including 64 critical care beds, 15 operating rooms (including Modular Ots), 2 Cath labs (including 1 hybrid Cath lab), 7 day-care procedure rooms and around 90 outpatient consulting MOMS. The hospital is being planned for the latest of clinical technology across core specialties as well as imaging and diagnostics. These include a Robotic surgical suite, 3T MRI, CT, PET-CT, SPECT -CT, Linear Accelerator, Cyber Knife, etc along with the complete suite of general imaging and diagnostic facilities. The hospital is planning to acquire the following accreditations: JCI (International arm of JCAHO) and NABH for the hospital in general, CAP for laboratories and HACCP for food and beverage services.\n\n • HNH already has a well-established Medical Research Society. The leadership intends to further build and enhance these programs in the new hospital. \n• The existing hospital already had a strong program for post graduate medical education in 12 specialties recognised by National Board of Examinations and diploma programs recognised by College of Physicians and Surgeons and M.Sc.\Ph.D. programs in Microbiology, Biochemistry and Applied Biology recognised by Mumbai University The hospital intends to continue offering these programs along with introduction of other training programs in the future for doctors as well as paramedical staff. In addition, the hospital also intends to continue operating their existing Nursing college which offers B.Sc. (Nursing) degree program.</string>
    <string-array name="relation">
        <item>Self</item>
        <item>Spouse</item>
        <item>Mother</item>
        <item>Father</item>
        <item>Daughter</item>
        <item>Son</item>
        <item>Friend</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
